<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>📋 Guides on Remote &#39;n Active</title>
    <link>https://remotenactive.com/tags/guides/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 📋 Guides on Remote &#39;n Active</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://remotenactive.com/tags/guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Jobs For Beginners: How and Where to Find Them</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/digital-nomad-jobs-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/digital-nomad-jobs-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>The idea of a digital nomad job is appealing, but it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to find one. It requires a lot of preparation and flexibility to succeed in this industry, so if you want to make this dream come true (and are willing to put in the work), I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled everything you need to know about how and where to find your ideal nomad job.
Virtual assistantThe first thing you need to know about virtual assistant jobs is that it&amp;rsquo;s a broad category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Guide On How To Find Your Remote Job</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-find-a-remote-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-find-a-remote-job/</guid>
      <description>Finding a remote job can feel like searching for a needle in a haystack. The good news? You don’t need to know where the needle is to find it! All you have to do is know what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for and how to search for it. To help you out, I&amp;rsquo;ve put together this handy guide on how best to find remote jobs.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get right into it.
Know what you&amp;rsquo;re looking forIf you are new to the remote work world, it’s likely that you have a lot of questions about what this type of employment is like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Remote Leadership?</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/what-is-remote-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/what-is-remote-leadership/</guid>
      <description>The new remote working realityRegardless of where you stand on this debate, the sudden and widespread shift to remote work has been a wake-up call for many organizations.

Remote leadership requires new skills and mindsets, but it also presents an opportunity for leaders to make their organizations more agile, innovative, and efficient.
A positive workplace culture is something that can be cultivated even from afar.
💡&amp;quot;In the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discord For Work - Here is how</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/discord-for-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/discord-for-work/</guid>
      <description>Discord For Work - Here is how
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it.
The vast world of remote working tools seems like an endless stream of names and icons fighting for your attention. I fully understand that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep track of how to use what and when.
Which is why I have done the work for you.
Let me introduce.
Discord for workYou might have heard of Discord.
If yes, I have a little surprise (🕵️‍♂️ pssst, look at the title of the article ☝🏽).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Guide to Remote Team Activities</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/essential-guide-to-remote-team-activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/essential-guide-to-remote-team-activities/</guid>
      <description>The Essential Guide to Remote Team ActivitiesThe modern workforce is shifting
With the current rise of safety requirements, available technology, and a globalized society, more people are working remotely than ever before.
These days it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon to be managing an entire team who never see one another in person.
However, the lack of face-to-face contact can be challenging for team members who need to collaborate closely on projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
