<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🎆 TRENDS on Remote &#39;n Active</title>
    <link>https://remotenactive.com/tags/trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🎆 TRENDS on Remote &#39;n Active</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://remotenactive.com/tags/trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>21 Fully Remote Companies You Can Apply To Today &#43; Links To All Career-Pages</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/fully-remote-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/fully-remote-companies/</guid>
      <description>Now remote work isn&amp;rsquo;t a trend, it&amp;rsquo;s the new way of doing business. You can find fully remote companies on the rise in almost every trade and industry. The world is becoming more connected, and the Internet makes it possible for us to collaborate with people from all over the globe.
But there&amp;rsquo;s another trend that’s been on the rise in recent years:
Fully Remote Companies.
What is a fully remote company?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Jobs For Beginners: How and Where to Find Them</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/digital-nomad-jobs-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/digital-nomad-jobs-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>The idea of a digital nomad job is appealing, but it&amp;rsquo;s not easy to find one. It requires a lot of preparation and flexibility to succeed in this industry, so if you want to make this dream come true (and are willing to put in the work), I&amp;rsquo;ve compiled everything you need to know about how and where to find your ideal nomad job.
Virtual assistantThe first thing you need to know about virtual assistant jobs is that it&amp;rsquo;s a broad category.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cancel All Meetings: The Power of Async Team Building</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/no-meetings-today-how-you-can-make-async-team-building-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/no-meetings-today-how-you-can-make-async-team-building-work/</guid>
      <description>Cancel All Meetings: The Power of Async Team Building
The world is changing, and so are the ways that companies work.
Today&amp;rsquo;s workforce is more mobile than ever before.
Employees aren&amp;rsquo;t required to be in an office on a daily basis, nor do they need to be physically located near their co-workers.
 Even if remote work turns out to be less productive on some metrics than others, reducing carbon-based emissions or the improving work-life balance could make up for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Want To Track Team Mood? Easy, Just Use This Free Template</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-track-your-remote-teams-mood-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-track-your-remote-teams-mood-template/</guid>
      <description>You Want To Track Team Mood? Easy, Just Use This Free Template
We all know that being in an office environment can sometimes be toxic, but what about working remotely?
With no one to bounce ideas off of or share your wins with, it&amp;rsquo;s easy for things to get lost in translation.
It turns out that the work-life balance for remote workers is just as important as it is for employees who are on site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Remote First Companies</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/best-remote-first-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/best-remote-first-companies/</guid>
      <description>Best Remote First CompaniesYou likely don&amp;rsquo;t need another list of companies that are hiring, but you do need to focus on the companies that have undergone a massive change in culture and practice, especially in the last 2 years.
These companies have gone from being just another startup to becoming leaders in the remote first world and thereby transforming the lives of thousands of workers.
Not only are they looking for top notch talent from all over the world, but they have made it a priority to build learning cultures, inclusive cultures and accessible cultures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
