<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🧘🏽‍♂️ Mindfulness on Remote &#39;n Active</title>
    <link>https://remotenactive.com/tags/%EF%B8%8F-mindfulness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🧘🏽‍♂️ Mindfulness on Remote &#39;n Active</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://remotenactive.com/tags/%EF%B8%8F-mindfulness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Stay Productive While Working Remotely</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-stay-productive-while-working-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-stay-productive-while-working-remotely/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever woken up feeling like you have been run over by a truck, only to notice you fell asleep at your laptop.

Again.
Remote work has been an invitation for overachievers to work even more thereby forgetting, about their personal life.
As you will soon see, there are other roads to discover.
In this guide, I will show you what you can do in order to stay productive, without hitting your head on your keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winter is coming: How to Reduce Stress as A Remote Leader Without Losing Your Cool</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/winter-is-coming-how-to-reduce-stress-as-a-remote-leader-without-losing-your-cool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/winter-is-coming-how-to-reduce-stress-as-a-remote-leader-without-losing-your-cool/</guid>
      <description>How to Reduce Stress as A Remote Leader
Working from home is a dream for many, but it can also be incredibly stressful.
I bet, you&amp;rsquo;ve experienced it yourself.
The challenges of Remote WorkIn fact, most people don&amp;rsquo;t realize this until they try to work remotely and then suddenly feel burned out.
As a solution, some remote workers plan their days down to the minute in order to make sure that they get everything done.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Want To Track Team Mood? Easy, Just Use This Free Template</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-track-your-remote-teams-mood-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-track-your-remote-teams-mood-template/</guid>
      <description>You Want To Track Team Mood? Easy, Just Use This Free Template
We all know that being in an office environment can sometimes be toxic, but what about working remotely?
With no one to bounce ideas off of or share your wins with, it&amp;rsquo;s easy for things to get lost in translation.
It turns out that the work-life balance for remote workers is just as important as it is for employees who are on site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
