<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🦸🏻‍♀️ LEADERSHIP on Remote &#39;n Active</title>
    <link>https://remotenactive.com/tags/%EF%B8%8F-leadership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🦸🏻‍♀️ LEADERSHIP on Remote &#39;n Active</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://remotenactive.com/tags/%EF%B8%8F-leadership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Put Together The Perfect Team</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-put-together-the-perfect-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-put-together-the-perfect-team/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced business environment, many teams are forced to work in virtual spaces.
In this article, we will look at the characteristics of productive teams, the challenges facing virtual teams and how to overcome them.
Characteristics of productive teamsWhen building a team, you need to think about the characteristics of productive teams.
You can&amp;rsquo;t just grab people in different departments and expect them to work together.
You need to have a sense of purpose, as well as efficient communication between your employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Remote Leadership?</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/what-is-remote-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/what-is-remote-leadership/</guid>
      <description>The new remote working realityRegardless of where you stand on this debate, the sudden and widespread shift to remote work has been a wake-up call for many organizations.

Remote leadership requires new skills and mindsets, but it also presents an opportunity for leaders to make their organizations more agile, innovative, and efficient.
A positive workplace culture is something that can be cultivated even from afar.
💡&amp;quot;In the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head of Remote - Here&#39;s what you need to know</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/head-of-remote-heres-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/head-of-remote-heres-what-you-need-to-know/</guid>
      <description>Head of Remote - Here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to know
No one has to tell you that the world is changing.
The workforce has shifted dramatically over the last few decades, and remote work is now more popular than ever.
With this shift in working styles, companies are looking for new ways to lead their employees from a distance.
This means that there&amp;rsquo;s been an increased demand for Head of Remote roles – but what exactly does it mean to be a Head of Remote?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
