<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>🧠 Productivity on Remote &#39;n Active</title>
    <link>https://remotenactive.com/tags/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 🧠 Productivity on Remote &#39;n Active</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://remotenactive.com/tags/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Guide On How To Find Your Remote Job</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-find-a-remote-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-find-a-remote-job/</guid>
      <description>Finding a remote job can feel like searching for a needle in a haystack. The good news? You don’t need to know where the needle is to find it! All you have to do is know what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for and how to search for it. To help you out, I&amp;rsquo;ve put together this handy guide on how best to find remote jobs.
Let&amp;rsquo;s get right into it.
Know what you&amp;rsquo;re looking forIf you are new to the remote work world, it’s likely that you have a lot of questions about what this type of employment is like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Unexpected Stay-Active-Hacks You Will Not Find on The First Page of Google</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/tips-to-stay-active-while-working-from-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/tips-to-stay-active-while-working-from-home/</guid>
      <description>We all get it.
Being active while working from home is really important.
Like really, really important.
💡&amp;quot;Most remote work is done while sitting at the computer or on the phone, which means employees can end up staying in one spot for a long period of time. All this can lead to an unhealthy, sedentary lifestyle.&amp;quot;
- Forbes
Thanks, Forbes.
If you run a Google Search on the topic you will notice, that nearly all articles point to the same direction of one of these three options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stay Productive While Working Remotely</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-stay-productive-while-working-remotely/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/how-to-stay-productive-while-working-remotely/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever woken up feeling like you have been run over by a truck, only to notice you fell asleep at your laptop.

Again.
Remote work has been an invitation for overachievers to work even more thereby forgetting, about their personal life.
As you will soon see, there are other roads to discover.
In this guide, I will show you what you can do in order to stay productive, without hitting your head on your keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A 3-Step Formula For You to Lead Your Remote Team With Confidence</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/lead-your-remote-team-with-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/lead-your-remote-team-with-confidence/</guid>
      <description>A 3-Step Formula For You to Lead Your Remote Team With Confidence
There’s nothing quite like the feeling of empowerment and collaboration that comes from leading a team.
But what if your team members don’t work in the office next to you?
What if they’re remote workers or you lead a distributed team?
What if they are in another city, state, or country?
No matter the location of your employees, it’s critical to lead them successfully.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Remote Activities In Under 60 Seconds</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/find-remote-activities-in-under-60-seconds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/find-remote-activities-in-under-60-seconds/</guid>
      <description>Find Remote Activities In Under 60 Seconds
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly important to maintain a happy &amp;amp; productive team.
Which is why we have created this time-saving resource for you.
A dynamic online list with 85+ tools, apps and activities for your remote team
Who is this for ? Remote Team Leaders who want to save time and do want to spend hours on Google searching for things to do HR Managers who want to inspire their teams and provide the company with hands on information to implement straight away Innovators searching for the next cool tool, app or emerging topic in the field of remote team building  How it works Research - Curated list of tools, activities and apps from all across the web (Googled for you) Filters - Easy to use filters to find the information you need in no time  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Remote First Companies</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/best-remote-first-companies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/best-remote-first-companies/</guid>
      <description>Best Remote First CompaniesYou likely don&amp;rsquo;t need another list of companies that are hiring, but you do need to focus on the companies that have undergone a massive change in culture and practice, especially in the last 2 years.
These companies have gone from being just another startup to becoming leaders in the remote first world and thereby transforming the lives of thousands of workers.
Not only are they looking for top notch talent from all over the world, but they have made it a priority to build learning cultures, inclusive cultures and accessible cultures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Remote Leaders Value The Benefits Of Games</title>
      <link>https://remotenactive.com/why-remote-leaders-value-the-benefits-of-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://remotenactive.com/why-remote-leaders-value-the-benefits-of-games/</guid>
      <description>Why Remote Leaders Value The Benefits Of Games
If you’ve ever worked with a team that is scattered through different locations, you know the difficulties of collaborating remotely.
 &amp;ldquo;Removing roadblocks to improve productivity is a key skillset of any remote manager.&amp;rdquo; - GitLab &amp;ldquo;Being a great remote manager&amp;rdquo;
 The challenges of working with a distributed team may be facing different geographical time zones, cultural differences, bad WiFi connections, or simply the loud background noises of a subway because your colleague took the call on the go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
